// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "2 × 4",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "2",
      "8",
      "12",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "3 × 7",
    answer: "21",
    options: [
      "12",
      "18",
      "21",
      "14"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "5 × 9",
    answer: "45",
    options: [
      "50",
      "45",
      "70",
      "30"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "3 × 3",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
      "12",
      "13",
      "9",
      "18"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "3 × 5",
    answer: "15",
    options: [
      "20",
      "25",
      "15",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "7 × 8",
    answer: "56",
    options: [
      "21",
      "38",
      "40",
      "56"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "3 × 5",
    answer: "15",
    options: [
      "20",
      "25",
      "15",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "6 × 5",
    answer: "30",
    options: [
      "20",
      "25",
      "30",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "3 × 8",
    answer: "24",
    options: [
      "40",
      "25",
      "24",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "9 × 8",
    answer: "72",
    options: [
      "40",
      "72",
      "80",
      "90"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "13 × 6",
    answer: "78",
    options: [
      "78",
      "52",
      "65",
      "72"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "15 × 3",
    answer: "45",
    options: [
      "45",
      "52",
      "75",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "17 × 8",
    answer: "136",
    options: [
      "80",
      "120",
      "126",
      "136"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "12 × 6",
    answer: "72",
    options: [
      "72",
      "62",
      "65",
      "70"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "14 × 8",
    answer: "112",
    options: [
      "128",
      "112",
      "130",
      "138"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "18 × 9",
    answer: "162",
    options: [
      "180",
      "126",
      "162",
      "108"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "17 × 7",
    answer: "119",
    options: [
      "102",
      "121",
      "96",
      "119"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "19 × 5",
    answer: "95",
    options: [
      "85",
      "100",
      "95",
      "115"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "14 × 6",
    answer: "84",
    options: [
      "90",
      "87",
      "92",
      "94"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "12 × 7",
    answer: "84",
    options: [
      "102",
      "84",
      "96",
      "120"
    ]
  },
];
